morning
早晨
Is there any new progress?
有新的进展吗？
I found this in the lost and found center
我在失物招领中心发现了这个
He probably lost it when he ran away.
估计是他逃跑的时候弄丢了。
Check departure date
看出发日期
September 5th
9 月 5 日
The day after Li Yi was killed
李毅被杀的第二天
I doubt Yin Tianhong’s ultimate goal
我怀疑尹天鸿的最终目的
Itu Li Yi
Itu Li Yi
if we hadn't met you
如果我们没有遇见你
Maybe he has escaped from Xiyuan
或许他已经逃出西苑了
So this is illegal forgery
所以这是非法伪造
You will also need to check with the ferry company.
您还需要咨询渡轮公司。
Strange things
怪事
Is this our company's certificate?
这是我们公司的证书吧？
but
但
There is no one named Liang Ren here.
这里没有一个叫梁任的人。
September 5th
9 月 5 日
Destination: Donggang
目的地： 东港
We suspect there's someone aboard the Desire
我们怀疑渴望号上有人
Help smuggle the robots to Donggang
帮助将机器人走私到东港
this
这
Has the ship arrived?
船到港了吗？
I want to meet the captain
我想见见队长
Just shipped it a few days ago
前几天刚发货回来
The captain also called him.
船长也给他打电话。
Xiao Li, please ask Captain Jiang to come to the office.
小李，请姜队长到办公室来一下。
Lao Chiang, both of them are smart investigators.
老蒋，他们俩都是聪明的侦查员。
Captain, I tell you the truth.
队长，我告诉你实话。
We suspect someone is using your cargo ship for smuggling
我们怀疑有人利用你们的货船进行走私
No, are you mistaken?
不会吧，你是不是搞错了？
Is this your ship number?
这是你的船号吗？
of
的
Have you met this person?
你见过这个人吗？
No
不
How many times have you gone to sea this year?
今年你出海了几次？
This is the tenth time this month, right?
这已经是这个月第十次了，对吧？
Have you noticed anything unusual during this time?
这段时间你有没有发现什么不寻常的事情？
In fact, in January this year
事实上，今年一月份
Something happened in the nearby waters
附近海域发生了一些事情
I don't know what case you want to investigate
我不知道你想调查什么案子
Is there any contact?
有联系吗？
what do you think
你怎么认为
There are unapproved foreign cargo ships
有未经批准的外国货船
Sailing towards Xiyuan waters
驶向西苑海域
As a result, he was arrested by the beach police
结果，他被海滩警察逮捕了
Everyone on the boat wanted to escape
当时船上的人都想逃
However, the storm at sea that day was very violent.
然而偏偏那天海上的风暴非常猛烈。
many people drowned
许多人被淹死
Later, while examining the body that washed up on the beach,
后来，在检查被冲上海滩的尸体时，
It turns out they are all robots
原来他们都是机器人
This even made the news
这还上了新闻
I have the impression
我对此有印象
You two, can you stop?
你们两个，能停下来吗？
Don't worry, we'll keep it a secret
别担心，我们会保守秘密
Thanks
谢谢
Very good, very good
非常好，非常好
But you better check it out
但你最好检查一下
eager crew
渴望船员
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me
如果您有任何疑问，请随时联系我
Definitely good
肯定好
where are we going now
我们现在要去哪里
night market
夜市
Why go to the night market?
为什么要去夜市？
Very close to the pier
离码头很近
Many sailors often go there to eat
很多水手经常去那里吃饭
I have a friend who does business there
我有一个朋友在那里做生意
Let's ask him first
我们先问问他
Boss
博斯
Cheng Nuo
Cheng Nuo
Now, wait a minute
现在，等一下
I'm very busy today
今天很忙
there are many people today
今天有很多人
sit, sit, sit
坐，坐，坐
He is Sun Yao
他就是孙尧
my high school classmates
我高中的同学
Enter the society after graduation
毕业后进入社会
he is a sailor
他是一名水手
sailor
水手
It pops up when I think of it
一想到就冒出来
Initially, the sailors did their job well
最初，水手们很好地完成了他们的工作
I had no choice but to come to the night market to set up a stall.
只好来到夜市摆摊。
I don't know how much longer I can hold on.
我不知道我还能坚持多久。
Sun Yao, what are you doing?
孙耀，你在做什么？
Come, come, come
来来来
Come quickly
快来
I am coming
我来了
who are you chatting with?
你在和谁聊天？
no one no one
没有人，没有人
home home
家庭 家庭
this is my boyfriend
这是我的男朋友
colleague
同事
By the way, this time I want to ask you
顺便说一句，这次我想问你
Have you met this person?
你见过这个人吗？
no effect
没有效果
What's wrong
怎么了
there is nothing
没有什么
correct
正确的
Our class will have a party tomorrow
我们班明天要举行聚会
are you going?
你要去吗？
Busy with work
忙于工作
No matter how busy you are, you have to go
即使再忙也得走
You haven't attended a class reunion in several years.
你已经好几年没有参加同学聚会了。
I really can't leave
我实在走不了
real
真实的
No matter what happens tomorrow
不管明天会发生什么
you must be there
你必须在那里
Something important needs to be announced
有重要事要宣布
The girl next to me is nice
我旁边的女孩很好
What to eat slowly?
慢慢吃什么？
Does this have anything to do with women?
这跟女人有关系吧？
what does he want to announce
他想宣布什么
It must be related to women
一定和女性有关
How could he say it himself?
他自己怎么能说出来呢？
I am a thousand-year-old prodigal who cannot be bound.
我是一个无法被束缚的千年浪子。
Look at the towel around his neck
看看他脖子上的毛巾
There are cartoon patterns on it
上面有卡通图案
Are there still stickers on the cups?
杯子上还贴着贴纸吗？
only
只是
He just lowered his head when replying to the message
回复消息时他只​​低着头
Still smiling
依然微笑
You'd better go to the party tomorrow
你最好明天去参加聚会
We rarely have real friends
我们很少有真正的朋友
Eat quickly. I'll take you home after you're done.
快吃吧，吃完我送你回家。
I'm not hungry, so I'll go back first.
我不饿，我先回去了。
Who created me?
谁创造了我？
What was my first obsession?
我最初的痴迷是什么？
The period after being raided brightly
被亮眼搜查后的这段时间
In the end what happened
到底发生了什么
Why
为什么
my memory will be in pieces
我的记忆将会支离破碎
Cheng Nuo heard that you are now working in Mingmo.
程诺听说你现在在明默工作。
How difficult is it to work there?
在那里工作有多困难？
The income should be high, right?
收入应该很高吧？
It doesn't matter
没关系
go! go! go
去！去！去
In what situations would you refuse to be assertive?
在什么情况下你会拒绝表现出自信？
your girlfriend
你女朋友
When did it happen
什么时候发生的
five or six months ago
五六个月前
Think about it, this is my best friend
想想看，这是我最好的朋友
halo
光环
Cheng Nuo
Cheng Nuo
Too much
太多了
let me introduce you to
让我向您介绍一下
introduce
介绍
Come on, hurry up
来吧，快点
let me tell you something
让我告诉你一件事
Today is our class reunion
今天是我们的同学聚会
Use this opportunity
利用这个机会
I want to share happy things with you
我想和你分享快乐的事
happiness
喜
I have been wandering at sea for five years
我在海上漂泊了五年
I really didn't expect that I would go ashore
我真的没想到我会上岸
never thought about it
从来没有想过
i can come up with an idea
我可以想出一个主意
how are you today?
今天怎么样？
we are together too
我们也在一起
Day 184
第 184 天
Marry me in one thought
一念之间嫁给我
marry him
嫁给他
Promise to marry me in one year
许一年要嫁给我
kiss a
吻一个
halo
光环
Hello, are you Mr. Cheng Nuo?
您好，请问您是程诺先生吗？
I'm the person in charge of Channel Ferry
我是 Channel Ferry 的负责人
we found something
我们发现了一些东西
Is it convenient for you to come here now?
您现在过来方便吗？
Okay, I'll be there in a minute
好的，我一会儿就到
sorry
对不起
I even called you on the weekends
我什至在周末给你打电话
Why are you being polite to me?
你为什么要对我客气？
thank you for the tea
谢谢你的茶
Then I'll just say it
那我就直接说
Kasus Chen Xinhui
Kasus Chen Xinhui
Why did you want to come to me?
你为什么想到来找我？
Why did you suddenly think of asking this?
怎么突然想到问这个？
there is nothing
没有什么
After working for a while
工作一段时间后
I seem to suddenly understand
我好像突然明白了
Your initial confusion and feelings are gone
你最初的困惑和感觉都消失了
I remember the beginning
我记得一开始
I read your article
我读了你写的文章
Child Psychology Paper
儿童心理学论文
It's mentioned in it
里面有提到
How to remind a traumatized child
如何提醒受创伤的孩子
open your heart again
再次打开你的心
according to me
据我说
You may have several different ideas
你可能有几种不同的想法
what is it? Is your work not going well lately?
它是什么？最近工作进展不顺利吗？
No
不
excuse me
打扰一下
How did we first meet?
我们是怎么第一次认识的？
I went back to school to give a speech
我回到学校去演讲
after the lecture
讲座结束后
Come and ask me some questions
你过来问我一些问题
So at this time we
所以这时候我们
Contact established
已建立联系
Do not you remember
你不记得了吗
You're not a robot, are you?
你不是机器人吧？
joke
开玩笑
a bit strange
有点奇怪
Cheng Nuo also asked me the same question recently
程诺最近也问了我同样的问题
Ask how we met
问我们是怎么认识的
Why do I suggest you go to improve your eyesight?
为什么我建议你去明目呢？
Yes
是的
Why is he asking you these questions?
他为什么问你这些问题？
I don't know either
我也不知道
perhaps
或许
He wants to know more about his partner
他想更多地了解他的伴侣
this is information
这是信息
This Xu Miao is the chief pursuer on the ship.
这个徐淼，正是船上的首席追击者。
Entry-exit joint inspection of crew life
船员生活出入境联检
He is responsible for everything, including finances.
他负责一切事务，包括财务。
What happened to these two complaints in early July?
7月初的这两起投诉到底发生了什么？
Last year, a crew member complained that he was withholding his quarterly bonus.
去年，一名船员抱怨他扣留了季度奖金。
and food subsidies
和食品补贴
But Xu Miao thinks
但徐淼认为
It was the other party who violated company regulations first.
是对方先违反了公司规定。
This is not a reduction, but a penalty.
这不是减少，而是罚款。
How do companies ultimately identify them?
企业最终如何识别它们？
The problem lies here
问题就出在这里
Staff questions
工作人员提问
We must check it out
我们一定要检查一下
But Xu Miao has a strong sense of self-esteem
但徐淼自尊心很强
He said I didn't trust him and wouldn't let me see his watch.
他说我不信任他，也不让我看他的手表。
He even quarreled with me
他还跟我吵架
I was just suspicious
我当时只是怀疑
Is this a misuse of public funds?
这是否属于滥用公共资金？
That's why I'm not allowed to look at my watch.
这就是为什么我不被允许看手表的原因。
So what to do in the end?
那么最后怎么处理呢？
When it comes to quarter-end accounting,
在谈到季末会计时，
The numbers are exactly the same.
数字完全一样。
Xu Miao probably felt that the company was suspicious of him.
徐淼估计是觉得公司怀疑他了。
I feel a little uncomfortable
我感觉有点不舒服
He resigned soon after
不久后他就辞职了
Yes, that's the problem
是的，这就是问题所在
I also talked to all the staff
我也和所有的工作人员谈过
In fact, a similar incident occurred only once last year.
事实上，类似的事件去年只发生过一次。
Where does Xu Miao work now?
徐淼现在在哪里工作？
He no longer goes to sea
他不再出海
maybe you want to take a break
也许你想休息一会儿
Do you have any influence on this person?
你对这个人有影响吗？
he is a fan
他是一个粉丝
There seemed to be nothing else going on.
似乎没有其他的事情了。
halo
光环
Sorry, something just happened
抱歉，刚刚发生了一些事情
Any new clues?
有新的线索吗？
Lang Ning's former chief of staff Xu Miao is very suspicious.
朗宁的前参谋长徐淼非常可疑。
I suspect he lost money gambling
我怀疑他赌博输了钱
That's why we embezzled public funds
这就是我们挪用公款的原因
This hole can be filled later
这个坑以后可以补
He was probably smuggled in with him.
他很可能是和他一起偷渡的。
I'll send you the address
我把地址发给你
Let's meet there
我们在那里见面吧
How's it going
情况如何
listen
听
Who are you looking for?
你在找谁？
Is your name Xu Miao?
你叫徐淼吗？
What's wrong
怎么了
I heard you can help people leave Xiyuan City
听说你可以帮助人离开西苑城
Who do you listen to?
你听谁的？
If there's no problem, leave quickly
如果没问题就快点走
This is your betting history on sports betting sites
这是您在体育博彩网站上的投注记录
How do you make up for losing so much?
失去了那么多之后要如何弥补呢？
If we go in now, we still have to talk.
如果我们现在进去的话还得谈谈
If not, see you at the police station
如果没有的话，警察局见
I don't understand what you are talking about
我不懂你在说什么
Okay, then don't regret it
好吧，那就不要后悔
There will soon be evidence
很快就有证据了
Incorrect
错误的
Wait a moment
等一下
that's right
这是正确的
When I was at the beginning of the year
我在年初的时候
i lost a lot of money
我损失了很多钱
At first I thought about using the spare money on the boat to make money.
起初我想过用船上的闲钱来赚钱。
I didn't expect it to end
没想到会结束
All discounted
全部打折
So you take people to smuggle
所以你带人去走私
What do you want to know?
你想知道什么？
do you know
你知道吗
i know this person
我认识这个人
I was waiting for him at the dock that day
那天我在码头等他
He didn't show up in the end
他最终没有出现
The order was finally empty.
订单终于空了。
Where do you find these customers?
您在哪里找到这些客户？
Clients and Perjury
客户和伪证
This is all provided by Brother Biao
这都是彪哥提供的
Then didn't he follow Brother Biao's path?
那他难道就没有走彪哥的路吗？
Brother Biao is the biggest black fish
彪哥是最大的黑鱼
Smuggling channels throughout Taiyuan
太原全境走私渠道
Everything is in Brother Biao's hands
一切都在彪哥手里
Others also want to do it
别人也想做
You must also have courage.
你还必须有勇气。
The smuggling route that my partner and I developed ourselves
我和伙伴自己开发的走私路线
This also requires Brother Biao’s approval.
这也需要彪哥的认可。
working normally
正常运作
Mitra
米特拉
You have accomplices
你还有同伙
He was the first to suggest smuggling.
他是第一个提出走私的人。
He is also the one who contacted Brother Biao
他也是联系彪哥的人
I'm responsible for getting people on board.
我负责让人们加入。
Is he also a cast member?
他也是剧组成员吗？
He is my former colleague
他是我以前的同事
What's his name
他叫什么名字
If I tell you, will the sin be lessened?
如果我告诉你，罪孽会不会减轻一些？
Do you want to say it or not?
你到底想说还是不想说？
he is
他是
Sun Yao
Sun Yao
Could you repeat that
你能再说一遍吗
What is he doing
他在做什么
He recently opened a stall at the Fukou Night Market.
他最近在渡口夜市开了一个摊位。
I want to talk to Sun Yao alone
我想和孙瑶单独谈谈
Although he is a bit impetuous
虽然他有点浮躁
But I still understand the big picture.
但我仍然了解大局。
it's not supposed to do anything like that
它不应该做那样的事情
Then I'll leave first
那我就先走了
An Qiu, let’s go first
安秋，我们先走吧
until tomorrow
直到明天
morning
早晨
How did we first meet?
我们是怎么第一次认识的？
Cheng Nuo also asked me the same question recently
程诺最近也问了我同样的问题
he drank too much
他喝太多了
Cheng Nuo
Cheng Nuo
Why did you come?
你为什么来？
too late
太晚了
I drank three bottles later.
后来我喝了三瓶。
let me give you new chopsticks
让我给你新筷子
sit here
在这里坐
let's talk
我们来谈谈吧
It's okay, keep going, keep going
没关系，继续，继续
Coming soon
很快到来
Come here quickly
快来这里吧
Why are you so serious?
你为什么这么认真？
I found someone today
我今天找到一个人
Namanya Xu Miao
Namanya Xu Miao
You know him, right?
你认识他，对吧？
I know my former colleagues
我认识我以前的同事
We will no longer contact you after this.
此后我们不再与您联系。
What's wrong
怎么了
Xu Miao took advantage of his position to lead people to smuggle
徐淼利用职务之便带人走私
He also provided a person
他还提供了一个人
that is you
那是你
How could he talk nonsense?
他怎么能胡言乱语呢？
Xu Miao also said
徐淼还说
You initiated all the smuggling.
所有的走私都是你发起的
Customers are also arranged by you
客户也是你安排的
Impossible Cheng Nuo
不可能的程诺
So, you haven’t done what I said.
所以，你还没有按照我说的去做。
No
不
Coming for both of you
为你们俩而来
Thank you for giving it to me.
谢谢你把它给我。
This person was originally going to board Xu Miao's ship
这个人原本是要登上徐淼的船的
Leaving Saiyuan
离开赛园
I suspect he had something to do with my mother's death
我怀疑他与我母亲的死有关
you really don't know
你真的不知道
Why smuggling?
为什么走私？
I need money
我需要钱
You know, I'm getting married soon
你知道吗，我很快就要结婚了
I want to give him a good home
我想给他一个好的家
I do this business
我做这个生意
You can't make money
是赚不到钱的
What if I have children in the future?
如果我将来有孩子怎么办？
How can I support this family?
我怎样才能养活这个家庭？
You are the first person to say this
你是第一个说这句话的人
Our own sailors have to be out there all year round.
我们自己的水手必须常年在外面漂流。
that's why i do it
这就是我这样做的原因
Now I feel like my income is not enough.
现在我觉得我的收入不够了。
Are they forcing you to buy a house or asking for an engagement gift?
他们强迫你买房子或索要订婚礼物吗？
Besides, why didn't you tell me you had no money?
再说了，你为什么不告诉我你没钱？
don't tell other students
不要告诉其他学生
I don't want to owe you anything
我不想欠你什么
tell me about this person
告诉我关于这个人的事
I don't know how to find my customers
我不知道如何找到我的客户
Who is he?
他到底是谁？
Does anyone know why we left Sai Yuan?
谁知道我们为什么离开西原？
Only Brother Biao knows
只有彪哥知道
He gave a false identity
他提供了假身份
he is a wanted criminal
他是一名通缉犯
Be careful
当心
But I've never seen it with my own eyes
但我从未亲眼见过
Cheng Nuo
Cheng Nuo
You won't give up on me just like that, will you?
你不会就这么放弃我吧？
Don't you plan to get married?
你不打算结婚吗？
Thanks
谢谢
Does your fiancé know?
你的未婚夫知道吗？
i never told him
我从来没有告诉过他
Don't do similar things again in the future
以后不要再做类似的事情
This is very irresponsible behavior on his part
这是他非常不负责任的行为
You said it yourself
你自己说的
Finally have a home
终于有家了
What would he do if you went to jail?
如果你进监狱他会做什么？
Appreciating the talent in front of you is the most important thing
欣赏眼前的人才是最重要的
How is your friend?
你的朋友好吗？
It's none of his business
这不关他的事
What we're looking for is the smuggler leader.
我们要找的是走私犯的头子
just to find it
只是为了找到它
Confirm the source of the fake identity
确认假身份的来源
I asked the second team to investigate the specific situation
我请第二组去调查具体情况
Zhou Chen in the Android smuggling case
周辰在安卓走私案中
get some information
获取一些信息
I gonna go see
我去看看
Here's a June report on Android smuggling
这是 6 月份有关 Android 走私的报告
According to our understanding
据我们了解
Xie Wenbiao and his two younger brothers were on the boat at that time
当时谢文标和他的两个弟弟在船上
By the way, Brother Biao’s real name is Xie Wenbiao
对了，彪哥的真名是谢文彪
The smuggling ship is about to enter the port.
走私船即将进港。
As a result, I saw law enforcement officers conducting surprise inspections at the docks.
结果，我看到执法人员在码头进行突击检查。
Xie Wenbiao saw no way to escape
谢文彪眼见无路可逃
He forced seven robots to jump into the sea with him
他强迫七个机器人和他一起跳海
he did run away
他确实逃跑了
All robots will sink
所有机器人都会沉没
Can't robots swim?
机器人不会游泳吗？
I have no idea
我不知道
But we did an autopsy
但我们做了尸检
Discover the bionic human body
发现仿生人体
There is a large amount of anesthetic residue
有大量麻醉药残留
Is giving the medicine first to facilitate transportation?
先给药是为了方便交通吧？
Yes, they thought they could get ashore.
是的，他们认为他们可以上岸。
Just wake up android
刚刚唤醒安卓
Who knew we would encounter a law enforcement boat?
谁知道我们会遇到执法船？
All the robots are sleeping.
所有的机器人都在睡觉。
Just jump into the sea
就跳进海里
Although I can swim
虽然我会游泳
The chance of survival is also very small
生存的机会也很小
only six bodies
只有六具尸体
It's still us
依然是我们
It took more than a week to find
花了一个多星期才找到
The other may have been swept away by the current.
另一艘可能已被海流冲走。
Why did you suddenly think of asking about this case?
怎么突然想起来问这个案子了？
Any new clues?
有新的线索吗？
This has nothing to do with this case
这与本案无关
Kami mencari Xie Wenbiao
Kami mencari Xie Wenbiao
He and the robot we are looking for
他和我们正在寻找的机器人
Contacted
已取得联系
By the way, do you know it exists?
顺便问一下，你知道它的存在吗？
He has just been arrested by the police and is being interrogated
他刚刚被警方逮捕并正在接受审问
Prepare to eliminate smuggling gangs
准备消灭走私团伙
Not yet announced
尚未公布
So don’t share it with others for now
所以暂时不要对外分享
very good
非常好
take me to see him
带我去见他
Is this a request or a command?
这是请求还是命令？
help
帮助
Xiaodong went to contact him.
小东去联系了。
If you have anything to ask, please let me know.
如果您有什么想问的，请告诉我。
Did you arrange this order?
这个订单是你安排的吗？
Who contacted you at that time?
当时谁联系你的？
Is this the man in the photo?
这是照片上的男人吗？
That should be him
那应该是他
I only talked to him on the phone
我只和他通了电话
Did he say that?
他有这么说吗？
Why give up Saiyuan?
为何放弃赛园？
I have no idea
我不知道
At that time, this order had not yet been issued to this person.
当时，这个命令还没有下达给这个人。
I said I won't remember it wrong
我说过我不会记错的
I gave it to Sun Yao like this
我就这样给了孙瑶
The woman upstairs is still alive
楼上那个女人还活着
What
什么
I asked the woman if she was still alive
我问这个女人是否还活着
There are indeed living robots.
确实有活生生的机器人。
You made it very clear
你说得很清楚
Is this girl a robot?
这个女孩是机器人吗？
The boat I was on
我当时坐的船
If I encounter a law enforcement ship, wouldn't I be unlucky?
万一碰到执法船那我岂不是倒霉了？
If not, my order
如果没有，我的订单
Su Zhouchen
苏周辰
The day after the smuggling incident
走私事件发生第二天
Have you checked Sun Yao’s family?
你查过孙尧的家人
In the end, people are still missed.
到最后，人还是被怀念了。
Wanbu
Wanbu
I'm very sorry
我很抱歉
This time I neglected my duty.
这次我疏忽了我的职责。
But now the evidence is compelling
但现在证据令人信服
You can ask Xu for proof of identity.
你可以向徐一年索要身份证明。
Cheng Nuo
Cheng Nuo
This time, the three of you will lead a team to collect evidence.
这次，你们三人将带队去收集证据。
A second team will work with you
第二团队将与您合作
Wanbu
Wanbu
Okay, that's it.
好的，就这样解决了
The report must also be submitted to the Immigration Service
该报告还必须提交给移民局
Must be done well
一定要做好
You all go
你们都去
minister
部长
I said it was solved
我说已经解决了
halo
光环
this is me
这就是我
tomorrow
明天
Do you want to come along?
你想一起去吗？
No
不
us
我们
haven't seen you for a long time
好久不见
I should have noticed
我应该注意到的
Sun Yao ingin melindungi Xu Yinian
Sun Yao ingin melindungi Xu Yinian
That's why you've been hiding it from me
这就是为什么你一直对我隐瞒
do you feel anxious
你是否感到焦虑
Sun Yao ditipu oleh Xu Yinian
Sun Yao ditipu oleh Xu Yinian
Still thinking about how to arrest someone?
还在想如何抓人吗？
I saw they complied
我看到他们遵守了
I believe Xu Nianniian’s feelings for Sun Yao
我相信徐一年对孙瑶的感情
that's right
这是正确的
I just don't know
我只是不知道
How should I talk to Sun Yao?
我该怎么跟孙瑶说话呢？
Dimana Xu Yinian?
Dimana Xu Yinian?
he is not at home
他不在家
Sun Yao
Sun Yao
Come this time
这次来
I know, I know you will come this time
我知道我就知道你这次会来
What do you want to ask?
你想问什么？
Sorry, I lied to you
抱歉，我骗了你
How did you know each other
你们是怎么认识的
Weak start to the year
年初表现疲弱
only a few guests
只有几个客人
I drank a lot of wine alone that day
那天我一个人喝了很多酒
get up
起床
This is where
这是哪里
my house
我的房子
You passed out on the beach, don't get me wrong.
你在海滩上昏倒了，别误会我的意思
The following are the recent messages this site has received
以下是本站近期收到的消息
Smuggling incident near Taiyuan Beach
西原海滩附近发生走私事件
It is understood that the cargo ship carries several robots
据了解，这艘货船载有数个机器人
Is Sun Yao at home?
孙瑶在家吗？
Sun Yao
Sun Yao
Is Sun Yao here?
孙瑶在吗？
Zai Zai Zai
Zai Zai Zai
You are Sun Yao
你是孙瑶
Canaan
迦南
There's something I want to know from you.
有件事我想从你那里知道。
Did you go to the beach this morning?
今天早上你去过海滩吗？
Some fishermen saw you drinking on the beach
有些渔民看到你在海滩上喝酒
What's wrong
怎么了
You just need to answer yes or no
你只需回答是或否
visited
拜访过
Have you ever seen anyone suspicious?
你见过可疑的人吗？
No
不
No special circumstances
无特殊情况
No, I was the only one drinking beer.
不，我是唯一一个喝啤酒的人。
Go home and sleep
回家睡觉
Who else is in your family?
你家里还有谁？
my sweetheart
我的爱人
He doesn't feel well today
他今天感觉不舒服
I fell asleep just after taking the medicine
我刚吃药就睡着了
How do you feel looking back?
回头看你有何感想？
Remember to contact us
记得联系我们哦
Thanks
谢谢
OK
好的
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I want to repay you
我想报答你
You don't have to pay me back
你不必还我钱
That's not why I saved you
这不是我救你的原因
use use
使用 使用
can I ask you a question
我可以问你一个问题
Are you a robot?
你是机器人吗？
you
你
you can say it slowly
你可以慢慢地说
I transferred to Saiyuan
我转学到赛园
I heard it was because someone offered a high price.
听说是因为有人出高价了
Come and buy from us
快来找我们购买吧
We spent a few days at sea
我们在海上呆了几天
Waiting to go ashore
等待上岸
Unexpectedly, I became the target of others.
没想到我却成为了别人的目标。
The stowaways asked us to jump into the sea and escape
偷渡者要求我们跳海逃跑
he said if he was caught
他说如果他被抓住
we will die
我们会死的
My original obsession was to make my master happy
我最初的执念是让我的主人高兴
Cannot refuse any request from the master
不能拒绝主人的任何要求
Quick to use
快速使用
Namaku Xu Yinian
Namaku Xu Yinian
My name is Sun Yao
我叫孙瑶
you were a sailor
你曾是一名水手
It must be fun to be a sailor, right?
成为一名水手一定很有趣吧？
happy
快乐的
Sailors just run around
水手们只是到处跑
Go to various places to eat various seafood
去各个地方吃各种海鲜
Anyway, my family is gone
无论如何，我的家人都走了
Don't worry
不用担心
Wherever I go, it's home
无论我走到哪里都是家
I am
我是
can i be your family
我可以成为你的家人吗
After Xu and I were together for a year,
我和许一年在一起之后，
I also have a start
我也有一个开始
The most important thing is that he gave me a home
最重要的是他给了我一个家
He is my spiritual support
他是我的精神支柱
Dimana Xu Yi Nian sekarang?
Dimana Xu Yi Nian sekarang?
I let go
我放手了
The further you go the better
你走得越远越好
never come back
永远不会回来
Cheng Nuo, please.
程诺，求你了。
For the sake of our two long-time brothers,
看在我们两个多年兄弟的份上
Leave it alone.
别管它吧。
don't let him go
别让他走
Sun Yao
Sun Yao
Didn’t you say that too?
你不是也这么说吗？
Appreciate the people around you
欣赏你周围的人
I beg you
我求求你
don't let him go
别让他走
great
伟大的
an idea
一个想法
Itu Xu Yinian
Itu Xu Yinian
Didn't I let you go?
我没让你走吗？
Why are you back?
你怎么又回来了？
I see people with bright eyes coming
我看到眼睛明亮的人来了
I'm worried something happened to you
我担心你出了什么事
Nona Xu Yinian
Nona Xu Yinian
Are you willing to marry Sun Yao?
你愿意嫁给孙瑶吗？
in sickness and health
在疾病和健康中
poor or rich
贫穷或富有
for life
为了一生
never leave
永远不离开
you want
你想要
I'm ready
我准备好了